blogsearchengine.com 2007-10-11

# » Privacy Policy - Blog Search Engine

Privacy Policy

No information is sold or released to anyone about visitors to this site or customers of Blog Search Engine without prior consent. In other words, no information is released to anyone unless you give permission first. This includes e-mail registration to mailing lists, or information requests. A user does not have to supply any personal information unless they decide to complete an information request or at their own will in sending email to employees or departments at Blog Search Engine.

Blog Search Engine does not attempt to collect personal information from children. If children do send personal information to Blog Search Engine , such as sending e-mail, filling out online forms,etc., the information is deleted. Note that Blog Search Engine cannot always determine that a user is a child.

Aggregate reports for web site visitors are generated. These reports do not contain any personally identifiable information.

Internet ‘cookies’ are used on this web site to eliminate certain content, such as pop-up boxes, from being served to the same visitor more than one time.

When visiting any Internet site your unique address called an “IP address” is recorded. Blog Search Engine does not release any information about the collection of this address to any third party except under court order. 

Blog Search Engine archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports, detect errors at the website, and for security reasons. The log files are eventually deleted.
